<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Roads - Hawaii County</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/Transportation/MapServer/6</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/centerlines_haw.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata]  Description:  Names and addresses of Streets and Roadways (major and minor) for the Island of Hawaii as of December 2020. Source: County of Hawaii, Planning Department. These road features were originally derived from Tiger Line files created for the Year 2000 Census data. Revised, December 2020.For additional information, please refer to complete metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/centerlines_haw.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, HI 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</abstract>
            <purpose>Names and addresses of Streets and Roadways (major and minor) for the Island of Hawaii as of December 2020.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Roads</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii County</themekey>
                <themekey>Street Centerlines</themekey>
                <themekey>Transportation</themekey>
                <themekey>HawaiiStateGIS</themekey>
                <themekey>histategis</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found.  Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>Hawaii County; Hawaii Statewide GIS Program</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20201031</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
